betbrain.com 2006-12-05

# BetBrain.com: Privacy Policy

| QuickBrain  
---  
Search  
---  

Most Popular  
---  
Popular Matches:  
FC Barcelo - SV Werder   
Chelsea - PFC Levski  
AS Roma - Valencia C  
FC Porto - Arsenal  
Galatasara - Liverpool  
FC Bayern - Internazio  
Olympiakos - FC Shakhta  
Tottenham - Middlesbro  
Charlton A - Blackburn   
Sporting L - FK Spartak  
AC Milan - OSC Lille  
PSV Eindho - FC Girondi  
Manchester - SL Benfica  
Hamburger - CSKA Mosco  
Newcastle - Reading  
  
Popular Outrights:  
Barb, WGC WC  
Eur, UEFA Champions Lea  
US, NFL  
Eng, Prem. Leag  
UK, UK Championship  

|  Privacy Policy  
---  
At BetBrain Limited we are committed to protecting your privacy. These terms set out the basis on which we hold personal information about you.   
  
**Collection of Personal Information**  
We do not collect your personal information where you simply browse our website. We do require that you supply personal information where you use services provided through our website.   
  
**Storage of Personal Information**  
The data controller of our website is BetBrain Limited whose registered office is 4 Buckingham Place, London SW1E 6HR, United Kingdom, company registration number 04240954, VAT number 805 1539 48. Our nominated data protection representative dealing with data protection issues is Gabriel Munteanu, who can be contacted at the following email address [gabriel.munteanu@betbrain.com](mailto:gabriel.munteanu@betbrain.com). The personal data collected by us on you will be evaluated periodically to determine whether we should continue to hold it. You will be notified from time to time through our mailings of the continued use of your personal data and be given the opportunity to notify us if you do not wish to continue to receive mailings. We will not be exporting your data outside the European Union and will only be storing the information supplied by you together with details of the activities you have undertaken with us and mailings we have sent to you on your data file.   
  
**Our use of Personal Information**  
We will only use the personal information you provide to us for the following purposes:   

* Communicating with you 
* Notifying you of information relating to our products and services 
* Processing a transaction between you and us.   
  
**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
While we do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others we may choose to do so in future with trustworthy and specified third parties. We will always endeavour to email you prior to any such transfer in order to gain your specific permission to transmit your data to such persons. We may need to disclose your personal information to third parties where this is required by law or where this is necessary for the performance of a service we provide to you.   
  
We may provide aggregate statistics about customers, sales, traffic patters and related site information to reputable third party vendors but these will not include any personally identifying information.   
  
**Your Consent**  
By using our web site, you consent to our collection and use of your personal data for the purposes set out above. In the event that we decide to change our privacy policy we will post such changes on this page in order that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
